(Leonard:)We're not selling
his tomatoes on eBay.
(Raj:)No, if we got Captain Reynolds
from Firefly
(Raj:)to do a signing
at Stuart's store,
(Howard:)that would be
amazing.
(Howard:)That would be great.
(Raj:)So should we go
talk to him?
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)I mean, if he's not nice,
it's gonna make it hard for me
(Leonard:)to watch him in
anything again.
What?!
The-the guy who plays
Jon Snow was a jerk.
(Raj:)We still watch
Game of Thrones.
(Leonard:)He was a jerk because
you rear-ended him.
(Raj:)I was distracted.
(Raj:)It's weird seeing a member
of the Night's Watch
(Raj:)with a kayak strapped
to his car.
(Raj:)Come on.
(groans)
KOOTHRAPPALI: Hi,
excuse me, s-s...
I-I don't mean
to bother you,
(Raj:)but we're just really
big fans of Firefly.
A-And Dr. Horrible.
(Nathan Fillion:)Oh, uh, I think
you made a mistake.
(Nathan Fillion:)I'm not an actor.
(Raj:)Don't say that.
(Raj:)I mean, you're not
Dame Judi Dench,
(Raj:)but you're
pretty great.